## Juan Duboue, CPA

15 Forstall Avenue Kenner, LA 70065 jrduboue@gmail.com Cell: (504) 218-6650

**Profile** 

Experienced finance professional with over ten years of experience in M&A, due diligence, strategic planning, and consulting

Expertise

Data analysis, strategic thinking, financial modeling, financial forecasting, due diligence, mergers & acquisitions, project management, leading cross-functional teams, leading multiple projects, relationship building, executive level communications, presentation development, vendor management

Experience

## Ochsner Health (New Orleans, LA)

Director of Strategic Business Development

Jul 2019 – Jul 2023

- Directed strategic acquisitions totaling over \$750MM in revenue, including health systems, surgery centers, urgent care centers, physician groups, and more
- Oversaw entire M&A function, advising executive leadership on valuation, business
  case, and deal structure while project managing the deal process, facilitating
  discussions with potential sellers, completing financial modeling and due diligence,
  reviewing legal documents, and participating in integration planning
- Provided ongoing industry trend updates and competitive intelligence to inform strategic business planning discussions with leadership
- Completed special projects as needed, offering guidance to executive leadership and service line leaders on strategic business planning

## Breslin, Young & Slaughter (Remote/Travel)

Senior Healthcare Financial Consultant Healthcare Financial Consultant Jan 2017 – Jun 2019 Jan 2015 – Dec 2016

- Led nationwide financial services consulting engagements, including pre-loan and loan monitoring field examinations, quality of earnings, and workout services for healthcare lending institutions
- Completed 30-40 engagements per year, delivering workpapers and reports offering valuable insights on availability, quality of revenue, cash flows, management, financial processes, financial condition, and credit risks
- Led engagement of company's largest recurring client line of credit with a commitment of \$500MM
- As an active contributor to BY&S' Work Product Committee, trained new and existing employees while enhancing processes and creating training documentation

## Postlethwaite & Netterville (Metairie, LA)

Staff Auditor Audit Intern Jan 2014 – Dec 2014

Jun 2013 – Aug 2013

 Provided audit and internal audit outsourcing services for various private and public companies across the Southern region and internationally

Education & Certifications

**Certified Public Accountant (CPA)** 

Louisiana, CPA.0029590

**University of New Orleans** 

B.S., Accounting, 2013

Le Cordon Bleu College of Austin

A.A.S., Culinary Arts, 2011